<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Unhappy Folk's Literature</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/</link><description>Recent content on The Unhappy Folk's Literature</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 11:11:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Critical Acclaim</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/critical-acclaim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/critical-acclaim/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/critical-acclaim.jpg"/>
Sought is individuality, charm, and wit. A praise is worth more than gold. Acknowledgement is a grant for correctness and likeability. It’s the company of others that provokes the need for conformity, when uncontrolled or unnoticed, it becomes an unwanted fellowship of convention, a wobbled pacing of thoughts and beliefs. Directed by the lunar tides of society.
Some retreat to solitude to see through the gray. Some accept the gray as the only true color for their lives.</description></item><item><title>Tongues of Flame</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/tongues-of-flame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/tongues-of-flame/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/tongues-of-flame.jpg"/>
Where there are so many, all speech becomes a debate without end. But two together may perhaps find wisdom. — J.R.R. Tolkien.
What would life be without our words? Why is it that we always talk too much for too long? What is it that we always waste our time talking about? And why do we never watch out for the paramount power our words hold?
A word can take a life.</description></item><item><title>Belonging</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/belonging/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/belonging/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/shipwreck.jpg"/>
I see an immortal tree. Breathing throughout the ages. Not counting days. Observing changes. Recording phrases of peoples’ brief phases. In different times and places.
I see mankind, divided and shrinking by the minute, and many minutes have passed. Where people would kill each other in the name of what’s most absurd.
But I must eat!
I see men, drawing lines to claim a piece of land, much like child play.</description></item><item><title>Soaring</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/soaring/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/soaring/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/soaring.jpg"/>
Whatever the pressure However your pleasure holds you Captive to the treasure – Marko Saaresto
Most of us are actually starving, seeking nothing but a warm meal every day. And this is quite the dream! Also, quite a lot can afford more than they themselves can comprehend. Yet it’s often the case that no one would even consider balancing this scale. Giving more than just a very little margin of what we own is considered almost heroic.</description></item><item><title>Craftsmanship</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/crasftsmanship/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/crasftsmanship/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/craftsmanship.jpg"/>
The value of one is often defined by what they do. The output of one&amp;rsquo;s work is not necessarily what makes it worthy. It is -like many other things- relative; some people consider a certain act heroic, while another group of people would deem it brute and evil. Who has the final word?
In the ever-miserable pursuit of illusory perpetual happiness, people can so easily adapt to committing certain actions they’d never do -willingly- if given the chance—just for all types of outcomes.</description></item><item><title>Even “Nothing” would be fair</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/fair-nothing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/fair-nothing/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/fair-nothing.jpg"/>
Justice can be relative; women were burned for witchcraft, and that was perceived by a majority of people as absolute justice. These majority later became a minority, and a new majority introduced a new absolute justice. This happened, is happening, and will continue to the world’s end. Because justice is nothing but pleasing a group of people based on flaky, and fragile rules made by the very same group of people.</description></item><item><title>Meek | Of “A” God</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/meek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/meek/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/meek.jpg"/>
Gods are everywhere and exist in various forms, Their definition is no longer what We used to perceive: an omnipotent, most powerful higher form. Now we have human “gods”. Some believe in multiple gods. Yet all these beliefs are for the same reason: Longing for the absolute truth.
If a god exists, then their rule is immutable; all creations must submit. There’s no other way. But since we have so many -alleged- gods with contradicting rules and laws, we are far away from absolution.</description></item><item><title>To the Roots (Reason)</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/reason/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/post/reason/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/img/reason.jpeg"/>
Everyone has their own reasons not to put an end to their lives. These reasons often are why many people actually consider putting an end to their life! Ironic and objectively sad. A marksman that mistakes a shadow for a prey sleeps his evenings with neither arrows nor a supper.
Everything that lives refrains from pain. We live our whole lives trying to keep the comfort/discomfort ratio balanced. A “pursuit of happiness” is a façade for an “escape from agony”.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.unhappyfolk.org/archive/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>